mindsharesurveys.com 2010-04-12

# Mindshare Surveys >> Take Paid Surveys for Money and Get Cash!

## MindShareSurveys.com Privacy Policy

MindShareSurveys.com takes your privacy seriously, and has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. Keep reading to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

### IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website. Your IP address, should you decide to register and/or create a MindShareSurveys account, is also used to help prevent you from creating duplicate accounts.

### Cookies

Upon your first visit to this web site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell us who you are. MindShareSurveys.com has two primary uses for its cookies.

First, we use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested.

Secondly, we use cookies as part of our authenticaton system when you login to your account. If you select the "remember me" option when logging in, our site will set a cookie so that you do not have to login again the next time you visit MindShareSurveys.com.

While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

### Information Gathering

This web site collects online contact information in various ways, including inquiry forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests. The information collected may be used to send the user information about our company, or to get in touch with the user when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/modify section below.

### Information Dissemination

We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via email. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

### Links to Other Sites

MindShareSurveys.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.

Also, via our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. MindShareSurveys.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

### Children Under 13

MindShareSurveys.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe MindShareSurveys.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

### Security

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

### Opt-Out/Modify

MindShareSurveys.com provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. You may do so in any of the following ways:

  1. Email: [support@mindsharesurveys.com](mailto:support@mindsharesurveys.com)
  2. Postal Mail: P.O. BOX 95281, Seattle, WA 98145

### Contacting MindShareSurveys.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us via one of the methods above.

This Privacy Policy was last updated December 1st, 2008.

### Get Paid To Take Surveys

So what's the deal with making money through online surveys? Is it really possible to do it? These are common questions a lot of people have when they first encounter the opportunity to get surveys for cash. I'm here to tell you that not only is it possible to make money, you can easily afford to pay off a lot of bills, gas, and groceries with the money you'll make for getting paid to do surveys. 

You might ask how it's possible. That's a very good question. You see, companies will pay you for filling out consumer opinion surveys because it's a very cheap and effective way for them to do their market research. Rather than paying millions of dollars for a large outside firm to do a study, they simply poll their users. 

So yes, you can definitely get paid for surveys. All it takes is signing up using our form, completely free of charge. In fact, you will never have to pay anything to do this. So go ahead and signup, and get started today!
